We use cookies to improve our services, make personal offers, and enhance your experience. If you do not accept optional cookies below, your experience may be affected. If you want to know more, please, read the [Cookie Policy](https://abdlfactory.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode "Cookie Policy")

Accept Cookies Custom Settings

Language

EN chevron-down

Currency
--------

EUR - Euro chevron-down

GBP - British Pound USD - US Dollar

Cart

Search  Search

[Shopping Bag](https://abdlfactory.com/checkout/cart/) **Shopping Bag**

loader

Loading...

x

**Checkout using your account**

Email Address

Password

Sign In [Forgot Your Password?](https://abdlfactory.com/customer/account/forgotpassword/)

**Checkout as a new customer**

Creating an account has many benefits:

* See order and shipping status
* Track order history
* Check out faster

1. [Home](https://abdlfactory.com/ "Go to Home Page")
2. / Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

**About our privacy policy**  

ABDLfactory cares a lot about your privacy. We therefore only process data that we need for (improving) our services and we handle the information we have collected about you and your use of our services with great care. We never make your data available to third parties for commercial purposes.

This privacy policy applies to the use of the website and the services provided by ABDLfactory. The commencement date for the validity of these conditions is 29-03-2024, with the publication of a new version the validity of all previous versions is cancelled. This Privacy Policy describes what information about you is collected by us, what this data is used for and with whom and under what conditions this data can possibly be shared with third parties. We also explain to you how we store your data and how we protect your data from misuse and what rights you have with regard to the personal data you provide us with.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact our privacy contact person, you will find the contact details at the end of our privacy policy.

* * *

**About the data processing**  

Below you can read how we process your data, where we save it, what security techniques we use and to whom the data are transparant.

* * *

**Webshop software**  
**Magento**  

Our webshop is developed with Magento software, we host our web store on a server under our own management. We have taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to prevent abuse, loss and corruption of data as much as possible. These security measures consist in any case of the application of SSL encryption and a strong password policy. Backups are regularly made to prevent data loss.

* * *

**Web hosting**  
**Transip**  

We accept web hosting and e-mail services from Transip. Transip processes personal data on our behalf and does not use your data for its own purposes. However, this party can collect metadata about the use of the services. These are not personal data. Transip has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to prevent loss and unauthorized use of your personal data. Transip is obliged to observe secrecy on the basis of the confidentiality agreement.

* * *

**E-mail and mailing lists**  
**Mailjet**  

We send our newsletters and transactional e-mails with Mailjet. Mailjet will never use your name and e-mail address for their own purposes. At the bottom of every newsletter e-mail sent via our website you will see an 'unsubscribe' link. You will no longer receive our newsletter after completion of the unsubscribe process. Your personal data is stored securely by Mailjet. Mailjet uses cookies and other internet technologies that make it clear whether e-mails are opened and read. Mailjet reserves the right to use your data for the further improvement of the service and to share information with third parties.

**Note:** If at any time you wish to opt out of receiving newsletters, please log in and go to account settings.

After registration your email address will only be used for emails with necessary information such as registration confirmation and password recovery email, updates regarding your order such as notification about order processing and shipping notification with parcel tracking info, order details such as address error, customs questions and other important order related questions. Registration for newsletter is optional.

* * *

**Payment processors**  
**Mollie**  

We use the Mollie platform to handle part of the payments in our web shop. Mollie processes your name, address and residence details and your payment details such as your bank account or credit card number. Mollie has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data. Mollie reserves the right to use your data to further improve the service and to share (anonymised) data with third parties. All the above-mentioned safeguards with regard to the protection of your personal data also apply to the parts of Mollie's services for which they engage third parties. Mollie does not store your data longer than is permitted by the legal terms.

**PayPal**

We use the PayPal platform to handle a part of the payments in our webshop. PayPal processes your name, address and residence details and your payment details such as your bank account or credit card number. PayPal has taken appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data. PayPal reserves the right to use your data to further improve the service and to share (anonymised) data with third parties. All the above-mentioned safeguards with regard to the protection of your personal data also apply to the parts of PayPal's services for which they engage third parties. PayPal does not retain your data for longer than is permitted by the legal terms.

* * *

**Shipping and logistics**  
**Sendcloud**  

If you place an order with us and indicate that it must be delivered via PostNL and DPD. We use the services of Sendcloud (PostNL and DPD) to carry out the deliveries. It is therefore necessary that we share your name, address and telephone number with Sendcloud. Sendcloud uses this information only for the purpose of executing the agreement. In case Sendcloud engages subcontractors, Sendcloud also makes your data available to these parties. Current subcontractors of Sendcloud PostNL and DPD.

**Fedex**

If you place an order with us and indicate that it must be delivered via Fedex. We use the services of Fedex for the execution of the deliveries. It is therefore necessary that we share your name, address and telephone number with Fedex. FedEx uses this information only for the purpose of executing the agreement. In case Fedex engages subcontractors, Fedex also makes your data available to these parties.

* * *

**Purpose of data processing**  
**General purpose of the processing**  

We only use your data for the benefit of our services. This means that the purpose of the processing is always directly related to the assignment you provide. We do not use your data for (targeted) marketing. If you share information with us and we use this information to contact you at a later date - other than at your request - we will ask you explicitly for this. Your information will not be shared with third parties, other than to comply with accounting and other administrative obligations. These third parties have all been kept confidential on the basis of the agreement between them and us or an oath or legal obligation.

**Automatically collected data**

Data that is automatically collected by our website is processed with the aim of further improving our services. This information (eg your IP address, web browser and operating system) is not personal data.

**Participation in tax and criminal investigation**

In some cases, ABDLfactory, on the basis of a legal obligation can be forced to share your data in connection with government tax or criminal investigations. In such a case, we are forced to share your data, but we will oppose this within the possibilities that the law offers us.

**Retention periods**

We keep your information as long as you are our client. This means that we keep your customer profile until you indicate that you no longer wish to use our services. If you want us to delete and anonymise your personal data from our database, you can do so by going to GDPR Tools below in footer. On the basis of applicable administrative obligations, we must keep invoices with your (personal) data, so we will keep this data for as long as the applicable term runs. However, employees no longer have access to your client profile and documents that we have produced in connection with your assignment.

**Your rights**

On the basis of the applicable Dutch and European legislation, you as a data subject have certain rights with regard to the personal data that is processed by or on behalf of us. We explain below which rights these are and how you can invoke these rights.

In principle, in order to prevent abuse, we will send copies of your data only to your already known e-mail address. In the event that you wish to receive the data at another e-mail address or for example by post, we will ask you to identify yourself. We keep records of completed requests, in the case of a deletion request we administer anonymous data. You will receive all copies and copies of data in the machine-readable data format that we use within our systems.

You have the right to file a complaint with the Dutch Data Protection Authority at any time if you suspect that we are using your personal data in the wrong way.

**Right of inspection**

You always have the right to inspect the data that we process or have processed that relate to your person or that can be traced back to you. You can submit a request to that effect to our privacy contact person. You will receive a response to your request within 30 days. If your request is granted, we will send you a copy of all data with an overview of the processors who have this data, with the e-mail address known to us, stating the category under which we have stored this data.

**Rectification right**

You always have the right to have the data that we process or have processed that relate to your person or that can be traced back to this. You can submit a request to that effect to our privacy contact person. You will receive a response to your request within 30 days. If your request is granted, we will send you a confirmation that the details have been changed on the e-mail address known to us.

**Right to restriction of processing**

You always have the right to limit the data that we process or have related to your person or that can be traced back to you. You can submit a request to that effect to our privacy contact person. You will receive a response to your request within 30 days. If your request is granted, we will send you a confirmation to the e-mail address known to us that the data until you cancel the restriction will no longer be processed.

**Right of transferability**

You always have the right to have the data that we process or have processed and that relate to your person or that can be traced back to you, performed by another party. You can submit a request to that effect to our privacy contact person. You will receive a response to your request within 30 days. If your request is granted, we will send you copies or copies of all information about you that we have processed or that have been processed by us by other processors or third parties on the e-mail address known to us. In all likelihood, we will no longer be able to continue the service in such a case, because the secure linking of data files can then no longer be guaranteed.

**Right of objection and other rights**

In such cases you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data by or on behalf of ABDLfactory. If you object, we will immediately stop the data processing pending the settlement of your objection. If your objection is well-founded, we will make copies and / or copies of data that we process or have made available to you and then permanently discontinue the processing. You also have the right not to be subject to automated individual decision making or profiling. We do not process your data in such a way that this right applies. If you believe that this is the case, please contact our contact person for privacy matters.

**GDPR Tools that you can use to modify all personal data that we keep from you can be found in your shop account settings.**

* * *

**Cookies from third parties**  

In the case that software solutions from third parties use cookies, this is stated in this privacy statement. Changes to the privacy policy We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time. On this page you will always find the most recent version. If the new privacy policy affects the way in which we process already collected data relating to you, we will notify you by e-mail.

**Cookies used by webshop with description**  

| Cookie name: | Duration: | Description: |
| --- | --- | --- |
| currency | 1 month | To remember personal webshop currency settings |
| language | 1 month | To remember personal webshop language settings |
| tracking | 3 years | For the affiliate system to keep track who send customers to webshop |
| \_\_atuvc | 13 months | For webshop software https urls |
| OCSESSID | browsingsession end | Webshop software uses this to keep you logged in during browsing |

* * *

**Terms and Conditions**

Also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://abdlfactory.com/terms) section establishing the use, disclaimers and limitations of liability for the use of our website.

Contact details person for privacy matters: M. Vos

**Useful Links**  

**Categories**

**Shop benefits:**  
  
\* Order volume discount up to 7.5% (for orders above €100 excl. VAT.)  
  
\* Always (shipped) in neutral packaging.  
  
\* Ordered and paid before 1:30 PM on workdays, shipped the same day.  
  
\* Everything that can be ordered is available from stock.

Webshop ABDLfactory is part of:  

Newsletter
----------

Email Address  

 I agree to my email being stored and used to receive information and commercial offers about your products and services

Subscribe

Copyright © 2024-ABDLfactory, All rights reserved.

x

I have read and accept

loader

Loading...

Done

Done
